Memorabilia Collection, 1782-2011 (bulk 1866-1997): Finding Aid AC053
University Archives
- Series 5: Dishware, 1801-2010; 102 boxes; 12 items
  - Class of 1978 popcorn bags, undated; 3 items (Box 96)
    Individual Chris Eisgruber, Eleanor McManus Moffat, and Dan Kinzer popcorn bags.
  - Class of 1988 20th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1988. 20th reunion. White plastic cup with "Lasso the 20th!" logo.
    AR.2009.023
  - Class of 1973 35th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1973. 35th reunion. White plastic cup with "First Class Memories" logo.
  - Class of 1998 10th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1998. 10th reunion. White plastic cup with bowling logo. "Going Back to Bowl Nassau."
  - Class of 1983 25th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1983. 25th reunion. White plastic cup with "83 Nation" shield logo.
  - Class of 1993 15th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1993. 15th reunion. White plastic cup with "Hawaii One Five-O" logo.
  - Class of 2003 5th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 2003. 5th reunion. White plastic cup with "What Happens at The Fifth, Stays at the Fifth."
  - Class of 1968 40th reunion cup, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1968. 40th reunion. White plastic cup with "Timeless" logo.
  - Reunion cup with guitar-playing tiger, 2008; 1 item (Box 1)
    White plastic cup with guitar-playing tiger logo.
  - Class fo 1939 beer can, 1964 June 11-14; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1939. 25th reunion. White can.
    AR.2009.009
  - Class of 1961 beer can, 1971; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1961. 10th reunion. Black can with tiger with "61 in 71" logo.
  - Class of 1955 beer can, 1980; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1955. 25th reunion. "'55/25th" logo, black lettering on orange background.
    AR.2009.024
  - Class of 1942 25th reunion glass, 1967 June 7-11; 1 item (Box 1)
    Class of 1942. 25th reunion. Glass with "42" logo and cartoon tiger.
  - USS Princeton CG 59 mug, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Teal mug called "Wonder Mug." Black lettering "USS Princeton CG 59" along with picture of ship
  - Espresso cup, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Ceramic with University seal.
    Gift of Charles Hathaway '23
  - Shot glass, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Orange and Black Princeton seal.
  - Mini mug with 1912, 1 item (Box 3)
    Seal and 1912.
  - Mini mug, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    U. seal. Green.
  - Mini mug with tiger head, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Tiger head. White.
  - Mini mug with tiger bust, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Tiger bust. Green.
  - Mini mug, tri-handled, 1952; 1 item (Box 3)
    Tri-handled, with U. seal and tiger bust. Green.
  - Mini mug with tiger, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Tiger and "Princeton." Orange.
  - Mini mug with U. seal, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    U. seal and "Princeton." White.
  - Mini mug with tiger bust, undated; 1 item (Box 3)
    Tiger bust. White.
  - Tower club mini mug, 1952; 1 item (Box 3)
    Princeton Tower Club, "House Parties '52."
  - Mini mug with 1912, 1 item (Box 3)
    Off-white, with shield and year.
  - Whiskey bottle, class of 1923, 1963; 1 item (Box 20)
    Class of 1923. 40th reunion bottle of Kentucky bourbon whiskey.
    AR.2004.063
  - Whiskey bottle, class of 1927, 1977; 1 item (Box 20)
    Class of 1927. 50th reunion bourbon whiskey bottle.
  - Water bottle, class of 1985, 2010; 1 item (Box 20)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. Orange bottle with black top and "Roarin' 25th" logo.
  - Whisky nip bottle, 1963; 1 item (Box 20)
    Bottled for reunions. "Old Forester"
  - Old spoon, undated; 1 item (Box 20)
    AR.1996.040
  - Class of 1924 60th reunion commemorative plate, 1984; 1 item (Box 20)
    Class of 1924.
    AR.2001.030
  - Silver spoon commemorating Frederick Brokaw, 1892; 1 item (Box 21)
    "Commemorating Frederick Brokaw of the Class of 1892 who died in July 1891 in an attempt to rescue a drowning woman at Elberon, N.J." A portrait and his name appear in the bowl of the spoon. Patent granted to Theodore Combes of Philadelphia. October 18, 1892.
    Given by James D. Zirin '61.
  - Silver spoon with football player, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    Silver spoon with football player and seal on handle.
    Given by William E. Bardusch, Jr. '39.
  - Small silver spoon, Samuel Miller Gardner, circa 1864; 1 item (Box 21)
    Note attached. "Old small spoon used by Samuel Miller Gardner through his days at Princeton College." Made by Daniel Hedgers, a silver smith of East Hampton, Long Island.
  - Sterling silver spoon, undated; 1 item (Box 21)
    University seal and black inlay design on handle.
    AR.2008.042
  - Class of 1949 beer can, 1974; 1 item (Box 23)
    25th for class of 1949, white.
  - Class of 1962 beer can, 1972; 1 item (Box 23)
    10th for 1962, white.
  - Class of 1947 beer can, 1972; 1 item (Box 23)
    25th for 1947, white.
  - Class of 1956 beer can, 1966; 1 item (Box 23)
    10th for 1956, white.
  - Class of 1941 beer can, 1966; 1 item (Box 23)
    25th for 1941, orange.
  - Class of 1940 reunions beer can, 1965; 1 item (Box 23)
    Class of 1940
  - Class of 1937 reunions beer can, 1967; 1 item (Box 23)
    30th for the class of 1937.
    Ira Dorian
  - Class of 1963 reunions beer can, 1973; 1 item (Box 23)
    10th for 1963, orange, tiger in space capsule.
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 item (Box 24)
    Short can, white, with tiger leaning on "P."
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 item (Box 24)
    Tall with black sticker of white tigers.
  - Class of 1959 beer can, 1969; 1 item (Box 24)
    10th for 1959, white.
  - Class of 1968 reunions beer can, 1973; 1 item (Box 24)
    Class of 1968
  - Class of 1935 reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 item (Box 24)
    Class of 1935
  - Reunions beer can with tiger on a keg, circa 1961-1970; 1 item (Box 24)
    Tiger lying on a keg.
  - Class of 1949 reunions beer can, 1964; 1 item (Box 24)
    Class of 1949
  - Class of 1937 reunions beer can, 1962; 1 item (Box 24)
    Class of 1937
  - Class of 1955 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1955. 55th reunion. White plastic cup with tiger blowing into horn. "Matt's Premium Beer."
    AR.2010.094
  - Class of 1965 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1965. 45th reunion. Orange plastic cup with "Sounds of '65" logo with record and tiger playing guitar.
  - Class of 1970 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1970. 40th reunion. White plastic cup with 1970 bug logo and Yuengling logo.
  - Class of 2005 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 2005. 5th reunion. White plastic cup with superhero tiger logo.
  - Class of 2000 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 2000. 10th reunion. White plastic cup with "'00 hangs 10" logo.
  - Class of 1995 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1995. 15th reunion. White plastic cup with black logo for "Top Tiger"
  - Class of 1980 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1980. 30th reunion. White plastic cup with "80 @ 30: Together Again" logo.
  - Class of 1975 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1975. 35th reunion. White plastic cup with "Millennium Moment" logo.
  - Class of 1960 reunions beer can, 1970 June 5; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1960. 10th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, circa 1961-1970; 1 item (Box 25)
    Tiger with various decade pennants, orange can
  - Class of 1942 reunions beer can, 1967; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1942
  - Class of 1926 reunions beer can, 1961; 1 item (Box 25)
    Class of 1926
  - Ceramic mug, 1914; 1 item (Box 28)
    Reunions.
  - Ceramic mug, 1915; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Ceramic mug with 1900, circa 1900; 1 item (Box 28)
    University seal and 1900 year.
    AR.1995.035
  - Ceramic mug, 1916; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Ceramic mug, 1915; 1 item (Box 28)
  - Ceramic mug with 1906, undated; 1 item (Box 28)
    Black, barrel shaped, 1906.
  - Ceramic mug of Thomas B. Hamilton, undated; 1 item (Box 28)
    Seal, "Thomas B Hamilton"
    E4825. Gift of the Nassau Club
  - Small wine bottle, 1974; 1 item (Box 28)
    Bottled for reunions. "Viniio do Tigre"
  - Class of 1915 mug, undated; 1 item (Box 29)
    Class of 1915. Off-white mug with orange University seal and black edges.
    AR.2005.091
  - Class of 1904 mug, undated; 1 item (Box 29)
    Class of 1904. Black mug with orange numbers overlapping each other.
  - Class of 1893 mug, 1903; 1 item (Box 29)
    Class of 1893. 10th reunion mug. Off-white with Princeton Shield and two tigers. "Charles H. Angell"
    AR.2007.003
  - Ceramic mug, 1914; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Ceramic mug, 1939; 1 item (Box 29)
  - Ceramic mug, 1913; 1 item (Box 29)
  - 1898 Grill Room mug, 1 item (Box 29)
    "1898 Grill Room Princeton"
  - L.S. Jadwin ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 29)
    Orange wing. "L.S. Jadwin"
    Gift of Emory M. Ford, Jr.
  - Ceramic mug with 1932, undated; 1 item (Box 30)
    Black, 1932.
  - Ceramic football-shaped mug, undated; 1 item (Box 30)
    Football shaped with University seal.
  - Ceramic mug, 1899; 1 item (Box 30)
    Reunions. "J.M. Shepherd"
  - Ceramic mug, 1902; 1 item (Box 30)
    Reunions. "William K. Prentice"
  - Ceramic mug, 1902; 1 item (Box 30)
    Reunions. "Peter Vredenburgh"
  - Ceramic mug, 1899; 1 item (Box 30)
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 30)
    Orange with seal.
    Gift of Sackett M Dickinson '05
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 30)
    White, orange and black with seal, tiger and pennants.
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 31)
    Brown, with university seal and pennants.
    EX5004
  - Glass shaker with shield, undated; 1 item (Box 31)
    with shield.
  - Ceramic Urn with campus buildings, undated; 1 item (Box 31)
    With Palmer Stadium, Blair Tower, Nassau hall and a roaring tiger.
  - Class of 1945 glass, 1990; 1 item (Box 32)
    Class of 1945. 45th reunion glass.
  - Class of 1904 glass, 1954; 1 item (Box 32)
    Class of 1904 50th Reunion glass.
  - Mug, undated; 1 item (Box 32)
    White mug with Princeton Shield and "Princeton" in Gothic print. Picture of three men in colonial garb.
  - Glass, undated; 1 item (Box 32)
    Princeton shield and motto.
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 32)
    "NBA 'We did our part'". Frank T. Buchner '34. Fundraiser?
  - Ceramic mug, 1904; 1 item (Box 32)
    Reunions. "Herbert J. Fraser"
    EX4822
  - Ceramic mug, 1904; 1 item (Box 32)
    Reunions. "William H. Tower"
  - Mug with football, undated; 1 item (Box 32)
    Orange with football on side, black handle.
  - Ceramic mug with 1934, undated; 1 item (Box 33)
    Black, 1934.
  - Ceramic mug from Freshman Prom, 1957; 1 item (Box 33)
    Black. "Freshman Prom 1957."
  - Bicentennial glass, 1956; 1 item (Box 33)
    Bicentennial glass with orange U. seal and Nassau Hall.
  - Glass, undated; 1 item (Box 33)
    Old U. seal and motto.
  - Princeton in Texas glass, 1954 March; 1 item (Box 33)
    "Princeton in Texas"
  - PAA of Maryland glass, 1957; 1 item (Box 33)
    PAA of Maryland. Dinner and Dance for Dodds.
  - Class fo 1926 bicentennial glass, 1956; 1 item (Box 33)
    Bicentennial, Class of 1926.
  - Glass with U. seal, undated; 1 item (Box 33)
    U. seal.
  - Prospect Club mini-mug, 1950; 1 item (Box 34)
    Miniature mug. "1950 House Party. Princeton Prospect Club."
    AR.2009.095
  - Class of 1931 mug, undated; 1 item (Box 34)
    Class of 1931. Black mug with gold insignia.
    AR.2011.046
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 34)
    White, with University seal.
  - Cannon Club mug, 1971; 1 item (Box 34)
    White with "Cannon Club Princeton University" in green. "James D. Hess."
  - Princeton-Yale score mug, undated; 1 item (Box 34)
    White with "P 27" in orange and black and "Y 2" in blue.
  - 1902 Decennial Reunion mug, 1912; 1 item (Box 34)
    "P 1902 Decennial Reunion" in black.
    AR.2000.111
  - Mini mug, 1907; 1 item (Box 34)
    Tri-handled reunions.
    EX4733
  - Small cup, undated; 1 item (Box 34)
    U. seal. White with gold trim set on square base.
  - Pewter mug "EMB", 1912; 1 item (Box 35)
    "EMB 1912" and signatures.
    AR.1996.022. Gift of Kenneth Barnhart '45.
  - Pewter mug "JBFW", 1933; 1 item (Box 35)
    "JBFW 1933 187" and signatures.
    EX4584 5
  - Pewter mug "Ned Benson", Ivy Club, 1899; 1 item (Box 35)
    "Ned Benson" Ivy Club seal 1899 and signatures.
    EX4588
  - Pewter mug "Lynn Adsit", Cottage Club, 1904; 1 item (Box 35)
    "Lynn M Adsit 1904" Cottage Club seal and signatures.
  - Pewter mug "JBF Wainwright", 1933; 1 item (Box 35)
    "JBF Wainwright '33" Wing engraved on mug.
    EX4584
  - Pewter mug "MCM Jr.", 1935; 1 item (Box 35)
    "MCM Jr. 1935 10"
  - Pewter mug "GR Brown", 1943; 1 item (Box 35)
    "GR Brown 1943 151"
  - Pewter mug "J. Nelson Carter", Cap and Gown, 1904; 1 item (Box 35)
    "J Nelson Carter 1904" Cap and Gown seal and signatures.
    Gift of J. Nelson Carter '04
  - Class of 1936 mug, 1956; 1 item (Box 37)
    Class of 1936. 20th reunion. Beer stein with Princeton logo. Initials printed "N. H. S."
    AR.2010.137; Received from Debbie Tillinghast. Possibly originally owned by Newton Hale Shaffer '36?
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box 37)
    Green with gold University seal.
    EX5003
  - Pewter mug "To Max Farrand", 1901; 1 item (Box 37)
    "To Max Farrand" with U. seal and signatures.
  - Pewter mug, undated; 1 item (Box 38)
  - Pewter mug "Fred JH Sutton", 1898; 1 item (Box 38)
    "Fred JH Sutton '98" and signatures.
    EX4574/1
  - Pewter mug "Billy Pell", Colonial Club, 1898; 1 item (Box 38)
    "Billy Pell" 1898 Colonial Club seal and signatures.
    EX4574/2
  - Ceramic Mug, undated; 1 item (Box 38)
    Princeton Shield.
  - Ceramic mug with 1909, undated; 1 item (Box 38)
    Tiger with Princeton shield, "1909" in orange. Black and green, gold trim, white inside.
    AR.2008.050
  - Ceramic mug with "P '09", undated; 1 item (Box 38)
    "P '09." Black with orange letters, gold trim, white inside.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, 1930; 13 items (Box 46)
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Complete set in original packaging.
    AR.2002.070
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, 1930; 12 items (Box 49)
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Near-complete set in original packaging. Duplicates of box A-1.
    EX4956 /1
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, 1930; 13 items (Box 50)
    EX4956 /2
  - Small plate with Nassau Hall, undated; 1 item (Box 51)
    Nassau Hall in center with border of red roses.
    AR.1997.079
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, undated; 8 items (Box 51)
    Cream colored, gold trim. Various campus views. Complete set. #41 of 100 sets made.
  - Class of 1911 30th reunion plate, 1941; 1 item (Box 51)
    Wedgwood. Class of 1911 seal with affixed description. Designed for 30th reunion by Curtis Fields.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, 1930; 12 items (Box 52)
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china.
    AR.2007.123
  - Class of 1970 cicada beer can holder, undated; 1 item (Box 54)
    1970 Princeton shield Cicada pattern.
  - Class of 1939 reunions beer can, 1969; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1939. 30th reunion.
    AR.2001.062
  - Class of 1953 reunions beer can, 1973; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1953. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, 1968; 1 item (Box 54)
    1968
  - Class of 1946 reunions beer can, 1971 June 3; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1946. 25th reunion.
  - Class of 1955 reunions beer can, 1975; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1955. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions plastic cup, undated; 1 item (Box 54)
    30th reunion. "It's about time" and a drunk tiger on top of an hourglass
  - Reunions plastic cup, 1988 June 2; 1 item (Box 54)
    "Reunions June 2-4 1988" and a drunk tiger on top of an hourglass
  - Class of 1939 reunions plastic cup, 1989 June 1; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1939. 50th reunion.
  - Class of 1969 reunions plastic cup, 1989 June 1; 1 item (Box 54)
    Class of 1969. 20th reunion.
  - Ceramic mug with P 1912, undated; 1 item (Box 55)
    Off-white with orange and black and "P 1912."
    AR.1998.025
  - Class of 1926 reunion glass, 1976; 1 item (Box 55)
    "1926 50th Reunion 1976" and mascot.
    AR.2000.023
  - Class of 1923 ceramic mug, 1948; 1 item (Box 55)
    Off-white with orange and black, "Princeton 1923-1948" with "23" encircled in center.
  - Ceramic mug with 1936, undated; 1 item (Box 55)
    White with seal and "Princeton University," "1936" and "Jac Weller."
  - Ceramic mug with football player, undated; 1 item (Box 55)
    Orange and black with shield in brown and football player on back.
  - Class of 1972 reunions plastic cup, 1992 June 4; 1 item (Box 55)
    Class of 1972. 20th reunion.
  - Class of 1983 reunions plastic cup, 1988 June 2; 1 item (Box 55)
    Class of 1983. 5th reunion.
  - Class of 1970 reunions plastic cup, 1990 June 7; 1 item (Box 55)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions plastic cup, undated; 1 item (Box 55)
    Leaping tiger and "Princeton Reunions" on front.
  - Class of 1951 ceramic mug with music box, undated; 1 item (Box 55)
    Princeton Shield. Class of 1951, "Charles Augustus Brothman." Music box in bottom, plays, "Going Back to Nassau Hall."
    AR.2008.024
  - Class of 1941 reunions beer can, 1962 June 7; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1942. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, undated; 1 item (Box 57)
    20th Reunion
  - Class of 1951 reunions beer can, 1971 June 3; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1951. 20th reunion.
  - Class of 1943 reunions beer can, 1968 June; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1943. 25th reunion.
  - Class of 1945 reunions beer can, 1970 June; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1945. 25th reunion.
  - Class of 1941 reunions beer can, 1971 June; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1941. 30th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, undated; 1 item (Box 57)
    "Welcome Princeton Alumni".
  - Class of 1952 reunions beer can, 1972 June 1; 1 item (Box 57)
    Class of 1952. 20th reunion.
  - Reunions beer can, Ole 55 Twentieth Utica Club, 1 item (Box 63)
    Miscellaneous beer can - Ole 55 Twentieth Utica Club
  - Beer glass, undated; 1 item (Box 63)
  - Beverage glass, undated; 1 item (Box 63)
  - Class of 1915 lowball glass, 1970 June 4; 1 item (Box 63)
    Class of 1915. 55th reunion.
    AR.2002.047
  - Sherry glass, undated; 1 item (Box 63)
  - Class of 1915 beverage glass, 1965 June 9; 1 item (Box 63)
    Class of 1915. 50th reunion.
  - Lowball glass, undated; 1 item (Box 63)
  - Class of 1932 reunions beer can, 1962; 1 item (Box 63)
    Class of 1932
  - Shirley Tilghman installation water bottle, 2001 September 28; 1 item (Box 64)
    From the Installation of Shirley M. Tilghman, 10th president of Princeton University.
  - Frist Campus Center plastic cup, undated; 1 item (Box 64)
    Frist Campus Center dining services plastic cup.
  - Class of 1970 reunions beer can, 1990; 1 item (Box 64)
    Class of 1970. 20th reunion. Tiger catching a cicada.
  - Class of 1970 reunions plastic cup, 2000 May 25; 1 item (Box 64)
    Class of 1970. 30th reunion. Cicada pattern and "Return of the Weevil Empire" on front. One duplicate.
  - Class of 1970 reunions plastic cup, 1995 May 25; 1 item (Box 64)
    Class of 1970. 25th reunion. Cicada pattern with "In Locusts Parentis Non Compos Mantis" on front.
  - Pewter mug with lid, undated; 1 item (Box 64)
    Princeton Shield. "Charles Augustus Brothman."
  - Frist center water bottle, undated; 1 item (Box 89)
    Frist Campus Center water bottle.
  - "Touchdown Club" scotch bottle, 1963; 1 item (Box 95)
    Bottled for reunions. "Touchdown Club"
  - Bread plate, undated; 1 item (Box 99)
    Orange, with Princeton University seal and motto.
  - Bread plate with McCosh Hall, 1960; 1 item (Box 99)
    Color reproduction of McCosh Hall
    EX4933. Gift of Mrs. Michael S. Lang.
  - Bread plate, undated; 1 item (Box 99)
    Small University seal on white plate.
  - Butter dish, undated; 1 item (Box 99)
    Small University seal on white dish.
  - Two egg servers, undated; 1 item (Box 99)
    White ceramic egg cups with University seal.
  - Pewter chalice, undated; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Presented to "John E Parker, Jr."
    E 4769. Gift of William J Hazel, received '53.
  - Sugar basket, 1855; 1 item (Box S-000007)
    Metal; Recovered from Nassau Hall fire of 1855.
    EX4258. Presented by W.H. Lyrie, class of 1890.
  - Pitcher with 89, circa 1889; 1 item (Box 111)
    Ceramic. Green with seal, "Princeton" on front, "89" on back.
  - Pitcher with dragon handle, undated; 1 item (Box 111)
    Ceramic. Green with dragon handle. Tiger lying on seal.
  - Mug with 1912, circa 1912; 1 item (Box 118)
    Ceramic. Green with seal and "1912."
  - Mug with 89, circa 1889; 1 item (Box 118)
    Ceramic. Green with tiger head breaking through seal. "89" on back.
  - Mug with 89, circa 1889; 1 item (Box 118)
    Ceramic. Green with stalking tiger and seal. "89" on back.
  - Ceramic mug, undated; 1 item (Box S-000008)
    Black and orange with metal rim.
    Gift of Cyril I. Nelson '48
  - Candlesticks, undated; 1 item (Box S-000008)
    Grey with U. seal.
  - Ceramic goblet, undated; 1 item (Box 124)
    1' tall, with University seal
    EX4493
  - Large tankard, McClure, 1899; 1 item (Box 137)
    Pewter. From the estate of Professor McClure. "From a fair Sinner to the Monks."
    EX4921; Presented by Mrs. E. Dudley Johnson
  - Class of 1877 tri-handled reunion cup, 1887; 1 item (Box 140)
    Class of 1877's 10th reunion. White with tigers, part of song "Old Nassau."
  - Class of 1985 reunion cup, 2010; 1 item (Box 142)
    Class of 1985. 25th reunion. White plastic cup with "Roarin' 25th" logo.
  - Glee Club silver bowl, 1968 May 12; 1 item (Box 149)
    Covered by blue cloth. Presented to Walter Nollner by the Princeton University Glee Club
    AR.2007.018
  - Companion plate to soup tureen, circa 1801-1900; 1 item (Box 155)
    White with pink roses. Belonged to George Goldie, director of athletics under president McCosh. See tureen in Box 188.
  - Black plastic tray with Nassau Hall, undated; 1 item (Box 156)
    Nassau Hall in silver.
    AR.1997.020
  - Soup tureen, circa 1801-1900; 1 item (Box 188)
    Ceramic. Pink rose pattern on white. Belonged to George Goldie, director of athletics under president McCosh. Letter attached.
    Gift of John A. Bryan (brother of Goldie's son in law), Feb 14, 1968.
  - Crystal goblet, undated; 1 item (Box 192)
    13 inches tall. Handpainted inscriptions.
    AR.2006.051; belonged to Allan Marquand, Class of 1874. Given by G. Allan Forsyth, Class of 1953.
  - Wedgwood dinner plates with campus views, 1930; 9 items (Box 180-181)
    1930 series. Campus views in blue dye on china. Duplicates of box A-1 and box 30.
    Gift of Mrs. Frank S. Hoag, Jr. in memory of Frank S. Hoag, Jr. '31.Response letter enclosed. AR.2020.012
  - Wine Bottle (empty) for the 25th Reunion of the Class of 1986, 2011; 1 item (Box 3)
    Label says "The Great Class of 1986, 25th; 25 Years of the Class of 1986"
    Gift of Peter Wayner '86.
  - Mrs. Harold Dodds USS Princeton platter, 1945; 1 item (Box 225)
    "Mrs. Harold W. Dodds sponsor of USS Princeton". Silver platter and case.
    Gift of Mrs. Harold W. Dodds
  - Class of 1931 drink coaster, 1971; 1 item (Box 45)
    Reunions. 1931's 40th in 1971. One duplicate.
  - Tile with view of Blair Hall, 1897, undated; 1 item (Box 109)
    View of Blair Hall 1897. White.
  - Class of 1970 25th reunion Chardonnay, 1995; 1 item (Box 114)
    1994 Sonoma County Chardonnay. Full bottle of wine specially labeled for Class of 1970's 25th reunion. Funny label on back.
  - White tile, undated; 1 item (Box 119)
    With University seal and motto. "Princeton."
  - East Pyne cocktail napkin or doily., circa 1930; 1 item (Box 121)
    Picture of East Pyne old library on it, and note explaining its history.
    AR.2001.054